Guide to the Ira Silverberg Papers MSS.110
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Group 3, Series V: Personal Files
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 41, Folder 58)
  - Photographs - negatives, undated (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - Photographs - negatives, undated (Box 41, Folder 60)
  - Photographs, October, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 61)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Photo: Ross, undated (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Photos: Ira Silverberg, undated (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Photos: Ira Silverberg, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Photos: Ira Silverberg, undated (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Photos: Ira Silverberg and Amy Scholder, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Photos: David Trinidad, undated (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Publicity photos - Ira Silverberg, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Photo of Linda Yablonsky in frame, July, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Postcards, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Postcard, undated, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Abe Silverberg memorial material and photos, undated (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Speech notes, March, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - Sketch - Steinitz, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - Taxes, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 57)
  - Taxes, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 58)
  - 25 Cats - Andy Warhol, undated (Box 42, Folder 59)
  - Xeroxed passport, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 60)
- Group 3, Series VI: Computer Files
  - Diskettes - files for various publishers, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 61)
  - The Playful World - Presce, Mark (diskette), undated (Box 42, Folder 62)
- Group 3, Series VII: Other Media
  - Armstrong, Sara Garden - Airplayers VHS and artists pahmplet, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Becoming Transhuman CR-Rom and cover letter, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - The Best Thief in the World - DVD, 2005 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Closed on Account of Rabies - audiocassettes, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - CNN / FN - Ira Silverberg (VHS), undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Editing from Prudence, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Hair Original London Cast Recording, February 24, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - MTV News (VHS), 1998 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Postcards from America trailer (VHS), undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Valley of the Dolls VHS (3 tapes), undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Theme from the Valley of the Dolls CD, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Valley of the Dolls audio cassettes, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Group 3, Series VIII: Books/Periodicals
  - The Advocate no. 572, March 12, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - An American Avant-Garde: First Wave - exhibit catalog, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - American Booskeller magazine, November, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - American Poet - The Journal of the Academy of American Poets, 1997 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Aperture publications catalog, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Art and Understanding magazine, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Art in America, 1990-12 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Aperture magazine no. 164, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Atlas of Literature, September, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Barneys New York Flip Book, undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Beat Scene no. 17, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Bette Midler souvenir programs, 1978, undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - The Black Rider BAMbill, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Bomb magazine, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Broadside - Folk Counterculture, April, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Charles Laughton booklet, undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Cinefantastique, April, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - City Lights catalogues, 1993-1996 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Cups no. 82, June 1997 - July 1997 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Dames at Sea - playbill, April, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - The Deadly Directory, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Details magazine, June, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Details magazine, January, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Discovering Antiques, undated (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Exact Change catalogue, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Festive zine Issue no. 6, undated (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Fiction Collective 2, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Futuresafe: The Present is The Future, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Gadfly magazine, August, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Gay Times, June, 192 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Giorno Poetry Systems Issue 19, undated (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Grove Press catalogs, Fall 1986 - Fall 1989 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Grove Press catalogs, Spring 1985 - 1987 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Grove Press Spring catalog / American Museum of Moving Image, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Grove / Atlantic catalog, Spring 1997 - Summer 1997 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Harpers vol. 283 no. 1695, August, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - High Risk Books catalog, November 1994 - March 1995 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Kansas Alumni, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Lambda Book Report vol 5.09, March, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Life magazine photocopy, November, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Lila Wallace Reader's Digest Fund Annual Report, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Luna Park 7, undated, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Mother Jones, February, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Mother Jones Fine Prints, undated (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - The Nation, March 17, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - N.E.A. Grant booklet, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - The New Museum program, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - The New Press catalog, Spring 1997 (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - New York magazine, October, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - The New Yorker, Auguest 18, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - Opera: A new Way of Listening - Alexander Waugh, undated, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Out Write conference program, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Outweek no. 94, April 17, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Paper magazine, February, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - Playbill and Evergreen Showbills, 1963-1969 (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - Poets and Writers vol. 25 issue 4, July 1997 - August 1997 (Box 44, Folder 49)
  - Psychology Today, August, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 50)
  - Publishers Weekly, February 1, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 51)
  - Publishers Weekly, January, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 52)
  - Publishers Weekly - photocopy, October, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 53)
  - Publishers Weekly, June 1997 - July 1997 (Box 44, Folder 54)
  - Publishing Trends vol. III no. 12, December, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 55)
  - Pulse magazine, February, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 56)
  - Quest, October, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 57)
  - Rain Taxi: A Review of Books, February, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 58)
  - RE/SEARCH publications catalogs, 1993, undated (Box 44, Folder 59)
  - The Return of the Reforgotten - program, Octiber 16, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 60)
  - Revolution: 500 Years of Struggle for Change, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - The San Francisco Review vol. 21.6, November 1996 - December 1996 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - The San Francisco Review of Books vol. 17 no 1, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - The San Francisco Review of Books vol. 20 no. 4, September 1995 - October 1995 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - S.A.S.E. Newsletter vol. 3 no. 3, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Serpent's Tail Press - packet, 1992-1997 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Small Press Distribution Annual Report, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Surreal magazine, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Weidenfeld and Nicolson catalogs, Fall 1986 - Spring 1989 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - World Art no. 13, undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Group 3, Series IX: Burroughs
  - Acker and Burroughs memorial, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Administrative, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Administrative, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Advertising etc, 1996-1997 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Airline Itinerary, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Beat Culture and the New America exhibit, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - The Burroughs Reader, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Call Me Burroughs audio cassettes, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Clignett Burroughs, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, January 1992 - February 1992 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, March 1992 - December 1992 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, January 1993 - February 1993 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, March 1993 - May 1993 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence and photos, July 24, 1996, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, September, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, October 1996 - December 1996 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, January, 1997 - March, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, April,1997 - May, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, June, 1997 - July, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, August 1997 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, September 1997, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, October, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, May, 1998 - September 1998, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2002 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Dead City Radio proofs, 1990, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Death of Joan Vollmer Burroughs - Grauerholz, James with related material and correspondence, 2002, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Domain name registries re. W. Burroughs, 1996-1998 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Everything is Permitted - proof copy, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Everything is Permitted - proof copy (photocopy), 1992 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Everything is Permitted - proof copy (photocopy), 1992 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Everything is Permitted: The Making of Naked Lunch - correspodence and agreements, 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Financial, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Galley mailing, undated, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - James Grauerholz Interview, undated, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Handwritten notes, undated (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Interview: Giorno, John with Burroughs, W.S., June 1993 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Interviews re Naked Lunch, undated, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Interview - W.S. Burroughs and Allen Ginsburg, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Invitation, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Itinerary, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Jilted: Dennis Cooper and the Tar-Baby (William Burroughs) - Grauerholz, James, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Just Say No to Drug Hysteria - Burroughs, William S., 1989 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Lists of shots and locations for film (Naked Lunch), undated (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Christopher Lucas - Painting, Sculpture, Collage (catalog), 1989 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Mailing list, August, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Naked Lunch, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Naked Lunch 40th anniversary, undated, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Naked Lunch Afterward - James Grauerholz, January, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Naked Lunch cast and crew interview and bios, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Naked Lunch cover proofs, undated, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Naked Lunch - Cronenberg, David and Burroughs, W.S. 2nd draft, March 5, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Naked Lunch film book draft, undated, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Naked Lunch film book release info, correspondence, agreement, production history, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Naked Lunch film portraits, undated, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Naked Lunch (film) press kit, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - The Naked Lunch - Grauerholz and Miles, 2000, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Naked Lunch shooting script, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Naked Lunch W.S. Burroughs, screenplay 5th draft, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - Naked Lunch layouts, captions, synopsis, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Naked Lunch preliminary product info, undated, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - Naked Lunch reissue intro, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - Names and addresses, undated (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - Nike Air Max2 commercial spot, July, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Note / memos, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Notes on Frisk W.S. Burroughs with cover letter, August, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Nova Convention, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Nova Convention, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Nova Convention, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Nuthing Sacred, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Oboro Gallery - William Burroughs, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Photos: Cronenberg, David (Naked Lunch, the Fly, Videodrome and Nightbreed, undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Photo - W.S.B. Kansas 1987 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Ports of Entry pamphlets, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Ports of Entry W.S. Burroughs, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Press material - W.S.B., 1990 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Press release, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Press release - LACMA, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Press - W.S.B. articles / tear sheets, 1990-1992 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Press - W.S.B. articles / tear sheets, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Press - W.S.B. articles / tear sheets, 1996-1997 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Press - W.S.B. articles / tear sheets, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Press - W.S.Burroughs Dead City Radio, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Press - W.S.B. article in Detour, August, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Press - W.S.B. obituary articles, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Proofs - Destroy All Rational Thought, undated, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Proofs - Word Virus, undated, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - River City Reunion, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - River City Reunion, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Selections from The Museum Blank Book - W.S.B., July, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Spare Ass Annie, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Strange Amazing and Mysterious Places intro, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Tribute to W.S. Burroughs, undated (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Tribute to W.S. B., 1997 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Tribute to W.S. B., August, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Undated W.S.B. material (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - The Valley - Burroughs and Haring drafts, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Various writings on Naked Lunch - Burroughs, Silverbergm etc., 1991 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - William S. Burroughs, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - W.S. Burroughs audio sampler, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - William S. Burroughs: A Bibliography 1953-1973. Cronenberg filmography, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - William S. Burroughs notes re. Dennis Cooper's Frisk, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, June, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, July, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, August, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, September, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, October, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, November, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 45)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, December, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 46)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, undated, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 47)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, January, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 48)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, February, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 49)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, March, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 50)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, April, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 51)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, May, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 52)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, June, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 53)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, July, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 54)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, August, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, September, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, October, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, November, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, December, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, undated, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, January, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, February, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, March, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, April, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, May, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, June, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, July, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, August, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, September, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, October, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, November, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, December, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, January, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, February, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, March, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, April, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, May, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, June, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, July, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, August, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - W.S.B. - correspondence, undated (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - W.S.B. LACMA protest letter, June 23, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - W.S. Burroughs Painting and Drawings pamphlet, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - W.S.B. photos, undated (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - W.S.B. photos, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - W.S.B. photos, August, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - W.S.B. photos - Burroughs funeral, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - W.S.B. photo and poem (unknown author), undated (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - W.S.B. photographs (photocopies), 1979, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - W.S.B. photos (photographs) for Best of William Burroughs on Giorno Poetry Systems, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - W.S.B. photo negative - Ports of Entry, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - W.S.B. photo negative - Ports of Entry, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - W.S.B. photo negative - Ports of Entry, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - W.S.B. photo negative - Ports of Entry, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 40)
  - W.S.B. photo negative - Ports of Entry, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 41)
  - W.S.B. photo negative - Ports of Entry, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - W.S.B. photos - Ports of Entry, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 43)
  - W.S.B. photographs Summer 1990 (Box 48, Folder 44)
  - W.S.B. Tony Shafrazi Gallery, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 45)
  - Word Virus - introduction, undated, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 46)
- Group 3, Series X: Ephemera
  - Firecracker Alternative Book Award - Serpent's Tail - High Risk Books, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Seal, undated (Box 49)
  - Tattoo kit, undated (Box 49)
  - White linen with pattern, undated (Box 49)
  - Pantyhose, undated (Box 49)
  - Shadow of the Dolls prescription "pill" mints (2 bottles), undated (Box 49)
  - Christmas tree glass globe with cockraoach from John Waters, undated (Box 49)
  - Sarcophogus, Undated; 110.2.0001; 1 item one painting (Object 110.2.0001)
    Scope and Contents
    Artist: Carl Apfelschnitt
    Paintings (visual works)
- Oversize I
  - Oversize I: Series IV
    - High Risk covers, 1991 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - High Risk 2 cover proof, 1994 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - High Risk general correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Oversize I: Series VIII
    - Bomb magazine, Spring 1991 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - The Chronicle Review and cover letter - Romano, Carlin, June, 2001 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Interview magazine, April 1997 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - L.A. Reader vol. 13 no. 25, April 5, 1991 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - New York Press vol. 4 no. 12, March, 1091 (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - The Village Voice, October 11, 1994 (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Voice Literary Supplement no. 93, March, 1991 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Oversize I: Series IX
    - Ghost of a Chance - William S. Burroughs, 1991 (Box 130, Folder 11)
- Oversize II
  - Oversize II: Series IV
    - Kathy Acker - Blood and Guts, undated, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Apfelschnitt poster, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Dennis Cooper posters, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Kitchen posters, 1989 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Jacqueline Susann posterboard, undated (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Oversize II: Series V
    - Autograph book, 1988 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Charcoal sketch "For Udo", 1979 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Ira baby pictures, undated (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Sardi's menu, 1964 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Oversize II: Series VIII
    - Tim Dlugos, 1991 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Express Books Literary Supplement, August, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Holiday magazine, November, 1967 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Interview magazine, January, 1991 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Interview magazine, October, 1991 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - The Saturday Evening Post (3 issues), 1968-1969 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - The Sunday Times Style, July 6, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - Oversize II: Series IX
    - William S. Burroughs - Cold City Gallery, 1989 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - W.S. Burroughs Nike Agreement, May, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Burroughs posterboard - Viking Press, undated (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Burroughs posterboard - Word Virus, undated (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - William S. Burroughs - Shafrazi Gallery, 1988 (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - Cursed From Birth proofs, undated (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - Junky 50th anniversary, 2002 (Box 104, Folder 23)
    - Vitra posters and Burroughs correspondence, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 24)
      - Oversize II: Series X
        - The Official Ronald Reagan Door Mat, undated (Box 104, Folder 25)